Lowell Thomas
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Lowell Thomas, 2.1.3.3.3
  - Publicity photographs [at the WJR radio microphone], circa 1940s; 1 (Box 1528)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas at desk with WJR radio microphone], [15 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs [at the WJR radio microphone], circa 1940s; 2 (Box 1528)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas at desk with WJR radio microphone], [22 copies], 1
  - Publicity photographs [at the radio microphone], circa 1930s - 1943; 3 (Box 1528)
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas at large desk and old microphone, portrait of man with sword on wall], 1
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas standing at microphone holding papers with fedora], 2
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas standing at microphone hand in fist], 3
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas posing at microphone], [2 copies], 4
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas sitting at NBC Blue microphone, man behind him], [3 copies], 5
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas sitting at NBC Blue microphone, reading Saturday Evening Post], 6
    - Publicity photograph: [Lowell Thomas sitting at NBC Blue microphone, reading Saturday Evening Post, looking down], 7